(Sheldon:)with the
whiter-than-Marshmallow-Fluff
(Sheldon:)Leonard Hofstadter.
(Priya:)Oh, my God.
(Leonard:)What's the big deal?
(Priya:)Trust me, it's a big deal.
(Leonard:)They're gonna find out
about me eventually, right?
(Priya:)Yeah, of course,
just not today.
(Sheldon:)20 seconds.
(Leonard:)Are you ashamed of me?
(Sheldon:)Of course not.
(Leonard:)Then why can't we
tell your parents?
(Priya:)Please, don't push this.
(Sheldon:)He does that all the time,
doesn't he? 15.
(Priya:)Okay, fine, Sheldon, you win.
Turn it off.
(Leonard:)No, he's bluffing.
(Sheldon:)I never bluff. Ten.
It's blackmail!
(Sheldon:)Nine.
We give up.
(Sheldon:)Eight.
This is ridiculous.
(Sheldon:)It's a laptop
with a full charge.
(Sheldon:)Honestly,
what do you see in him?
(Priya:)Give him what he wants
or we're done.
(Leonard:)Three.
Really?
(Sheldon:)Two.
Okay, I'll sign it!
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Self-destruct sequence aborted.
(Sheldon:)You may have gone
to Cambridge,
(Sheldon:)but I'm an honorary graduate
of Starfleet Academy.